# **Kyaw Soe Win**

#### **Personal Detail**

#### **Address**

No (7) Room 2 Mar Lar Nwe Street, Tamwe Township, Yangon

### Phone

09459092375

#### E-mail

Kyawsoewin29894@gmail.com

## Date of birth

29.08.1994

#### Skills

- Android
- Java
- JSON
- SQL Fundamentals
- UML
- Project Management
- SDLC
- Kotlin

#### Certificate

• Project Management (Executive Institute Academy)

## Strength

- Team Player
- Problem Solving
- Fast Learner

## Language

English



#### CAREER OBJECTIVE

To work as an android developer in an organization where I can utilize my skills and knowledge related to mobile development and develop robust applications.

## **CORE QUALIFICATIONS**

- Known for writing efficient, maintainable and reusable code
- Experienced in interaction between various devices and version of Android
- Strong knowledge of Android SDK, different versions of Android and how to deal with different screen sizes
- Experienced in code versioning tools and release systems such as Git
- Familiarity with RESTful APIs to connect Android applications to back-end services
- Strong knowledge of Android UI design principles and patterns
- Knowledge of agile SCRUM, Git and Atlassian toolset
- Experience with Unit Testing
- Experience with 2D charting
- Familiarity with cloud message APIs and push notifications
- Experience with VOIP Integration

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Science and Technology (2016) Yadanarpon Cyber City, Mandalay

### **ABOUT ME**

Graduated from Yadanarpon Cyber City (YCC). I made three projects as I mention below at my university. After graduated, I started on job training at 72 Coder Company about one month. I made one freelance project in a week. I worked as Junior Android Developer at Trustinno Company. I have not only technology knowledge but also project management knowledge. I am worked as Junior Android Developer at MyanCare Company. I and currently working at Justlogin (Myanmar) Co., Ltd. I work as freelancer too.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### 72 Coder Company

#### **Intership Android Developer** (5/05/2017 – 31/05/2017)

#### **Mobile Doctor**

- Develop application using java
- Testing Application

#### Trustinno Company

## Junior Android Developer (7/06/2017 - 31/03/2018) Jobready365

- Integrate REST API with retrofit
- Use SQLite for storage
- Use Glide Library for loading Photo
- Use Git for development

#### MyanmarInfoCenter

- Integrate REST API with retrofit
- Use Picasso Library for loading Photo
- Develop application with MVP Architecture
- Use Git for development

#### MyanmarJobCenter

- Integrate REST API with retrofit
- Develop application with MVP Architecture
- Use Git for development
- Integrate with firebase for push notification

#### MyanCare

## Junior Android Developer (1/04/2018 – 6/12/2018)

## MyanCare/MyanCare Doctor

- Integrate REST API with retrofit
- Use Git for development
- Integration with firebase for push notification
- Use Jira for issue tracking system
- Integrate VOIP using sinch server

#### Skylark IT Solutions and Managed Service Co., Ltd

# Junior Android Developer (1/04/2018 – 6/12/2018)

## Hohodidi/Hohodidi Merchant

- Integrate REST API with retrofit
- Use Git for development
- Integration with firebase for push notification
- Use Jira for issue tracking system
- Integrate VOIP using sinch server

#### Justlogin (Myanmar) Co., Ltd.

## ${\bf Junior\ Android\ Developer\ (1/05/2018-Present)}$

## Justlogin

- Ensure application is properly integrated with Android APIs
- Contribute and participate in new feature product specifications
- Translate Designs and wireframes into high quality code

- Design, build and maintain high performance, reusable and reliable Java code
- Identify and correct bottlenecks and fix bugs
- Using Clean Architecture